<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet title="CSS_formatting" type="text/css" href="http://tools.ietf.org/css/rss.css"?>
<?xml-stylesheet title="XSL_formatting" type="text/xml" href="/tools/id_rss/smb_rss2html.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
><channel>
<!-- Generated with Perl's XML::RSS::SimpleGen v11.11 -->

<link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/</link>
<title>New Current Internet Drafts (All Categories)</title>
<description>New Current Internet Drafts (All Categories)</description>
<language>en</language>
<lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 11:26:04 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
<sy:updateBase>1970-01-01T00:30+00:00</sy:updateBase>
<ttl>60</ttl>
<webMaster>henrik@levkowetz.com</webMaster>
<docs>http://www.interglacial.com/rss/about.html</docs>

<item>
  <title>"Ericsson TWAMP Value-Added Octets" - Steve Baillargeon, Christofer Flinta, Andreas Johnsson, Svante Ekelin</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-ippm-twamp-value-added-octets-05.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-23, rev -05: This memo describes an extension to the TWAMP test protocol for identifying and managing packet trains, which enables measuring capacity metrics like the available path capacity, tight section capacity and UDP delivery rate in the forward and reverse path directions.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Publishing the "Tao of the IETF" as a Web Page" - Paul Hoffman</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/hoffman-tao-as-web-page-04.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-23, rev -04: This document describes how the "Tao of the IETF", which was published as a series of RFCs in the past, is instead being published as a web page. It also contains the procedure for publishing and editing that web page.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"ASON Routing for OSPFv2 Protocols" - Andrew Malis, Acee Lindem, Papadimitriou Dimitri</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-ccamp-rfc5787bis-05.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-20, rev -05: The ITU-T has defined an architecture and requirements for operating an Automatically Switched Optical Network (ASON).</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"The Atom "deleted-entry" Element" - James Snell</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/snell-atompub-tombstones-18.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-20, rev -18: This specification adds mechanisms to the Atom Syndication Format which publishers of Atom Feed and Entry documents can use to explicitly identify Atom entries that have been removed.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Applicability of LDP Label Advertisement Mode" - Kamran Raza, Luca Martini, Nicolai Leymann, Sami Boutros</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/raza-mpls-ldp-applicability-label-adv-03.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-17, rev -03: An LDP speaker negotiates the label advertisement mode with its LDP peer at the time of session establishment. Although different applications sharing the same LDP session may need different modes of label distribution and advertisement, there is only one type of label advertisement mode that is negotiated and used per LDP session. This document clarifies the use and the applicability of session's negotiated label advertisement mode, and categorizes LDP applications into two broad categories of negotiated mode-bound and mode-independent applications. The document also suggests an update to RFC 5036 and RFC 4447 to remove any ambiquity and conflict in the area of using correct label advertisement mode for a given application.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"DMM Comparison Matrix" - Charles Perkins, Dapeng Liu, Wen Luo</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/perkins-dmm-matrix-04.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-17, rev -04: Distributed Mobility Management (DMM) is proposed as a way to enable scalable growth of mobile core networks so that network service providers can meet new requirements for performance and reduced operational expenditures. This requires reconsideration of existing approaches within the IETF and elsewhere in order to determine which if any such approaches may be used as part of a DMM solution.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"MIF API consideration" - Dapeng Liu, Ted Lemon, Yuri Ismailov, Zhen Cao</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-mif-api-extension-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-17, rev -01: This document describes an abstract API that provides the minimal functionality required for a program to communicate effectively with peers and services on the network while running on a host that has more than one active network interface. This API is abstract: we describe the functionality that must be provided, not the bindings that should be used to provide that functionality. The functionality described here provides the building blocks from which higher-level APIs might be built, and is not intended to be used directly by typical applications.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Scenarios of IPv4 sunsetting" - Cathy Zhou, Tina Tsou, Chris Grundemann</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/zhou-sunset4-scenarios-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-17, rev -01: This document describes scenarios at subscriber, carrier and enterprise sites during IPv4 sunsetting. In each site, there may be different requirements and issues. The aim of this document is to put forward some issues in these scenarios and to identify whether further specifications are needed to solve these issues to facilitate IPv4 sunsetting.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"The Tao of IETF: A Novice's Guide to the Internet Engineering Task Force" - Paul Hoffman</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/hoffman-tao4677bis-16.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-17, rev -16: This document describes the inner workings of IETF meetings and Working Groups, discusses organizations related to the IETF, and introduces the standards process. It is not a formal IETF process document but instead an informational overview.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"802.1aq and 802.1Qbp Support over EVPN" - David Allan, Jeff Tantsura, Don Fedyk, Ali Sajassi</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/allan-l2vpn-spbm-evpn-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: This document describes how Ethernet Shortest Path Bridging - MAC mode (802.1aq) and (802.1Qbp) can be combined with EVPN in a way that interworks with PBB-MESs as described in the PBB-EVPN solution in a way that permits operational isolation of each Ethernet network subtending an EVPN core while supporting full interworking between the 3 variations of Ethernet operation.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"A Common API for Transparent Hybrid Multicast" - Matthias Waehlisch, Thomas Schmidt, Stig Venaas</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/irtf-samrg-common-api-05.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -05: Group communication services exist in a large variety of flavors, and technical implementations at different protocol layers. Multicast data distribution is most efficiently performed on the lowest available layer, but a heterogeneous deployment status of multicast technologies throughout the Internet requires an adaptive service binding at runtime. Today, it is difficult to write an application that runs everywhere and at the same time makes use of the most efficient multicast service available in the network. Facing robustness requirements, developers are frequently forced to use a stable, upper layer protocol provided by the application itself. This document describes a common multicast API that is suitable for transparent communication in underlay and overlay, and grants access to the different multicast flavors. It proposes an abstract naming by multicast URIs and discusses mapping mechanisms between different namespaces and distribution technologies. Additionally, it describes the application of this API for building gateways that interconnect current multicast domains throughout the Internet.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"A Forward-Search P2P TE LSP Inter-Domain Path Computation" - Huaimo Chen, Dhruv Dhody</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/chen-pce-forward-search-p2p-path-computation-04.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -04: This document presents a forward search procedure for computing paths for Point-to-Point (P2P) Traffic Engineering (TE) Label Switched Paths (LSPs) crossing a number of domains using multiple Path Computation Elements (PCEs). In addition, extensions to the Path Computation Element Communication Protocol (PCEP) for supporting the forward search procedure are described.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"A Framework and Data Model for Queries about Telephone-Related Queries (TeRQ)" - Jon Peterson</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/peterson-terq-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: As telephone services migrate to the Internet, Internet applications require access to diverse information about telephone numbers. ENUM, for example, applied the DNS to the problem of finding URIs for telephone services on the Internet. The intrinsic limitations in the query/response semantics of the DNS, however, have often been strained by the requirements for accessing information about telephone numbers. This document therefore proposes a protocol- independent framework and data model for querying and responding to requests concerning telephone numbers and call routing that allows a richer expression of both questions and answers.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"A Framework and Problem Statement for Flow-associated Middlebox State Migration" - Gu Yingjie, Melinda Shore, Senthil Sivakumar</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/gu-statemigration-framework-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: This document presents an initial framework and discussion of the problem of transferring middlebox (for example, firewall or NAT) flow-coupled state from one middlebox to another while the flow is still active. This has most recently come up in the context of virtual machine (VM) migration between hypervisors, but it is a problem that has appeared in other situations, as well. We present some of the parameters of the problem, define some language for discussing the problem, and begin to identify a path forward for addressing it.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"A Mechanism for Transporting User to User Call Control Information in SIP" - Alan Johnston, James Rafferty</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-cuss-sip-uui-07.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -07: There is a class of applications which benefit from using SIP to exchange User to User Information (UUI) data during session establishment. This information, known as call control UUI data, is a small piece of data inserted by an application initiating the session, and utilized by an application accepting the session. The rules which apply for a specific application are defined by a UUI package. This UUI data is opaque to SIP and its function is unrelated to any basic SIP function. This document defines a new SIP header field, User-to-User, to transport UUI data, along with an extension mechanism.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"A Publication Protocol for the Resource Public Key Infrastructure (RPKI)" - Samuel Weiler, Anuja Sonalker, Rob Austein</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-sidr-publication-03.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -03: This document defines a protocol for publishing Resource Public Key Infrastructure (RPKI) objects. Even though the RPKI will have many participants issuing certificates and creating other objects, it is operationally useful to consolidate the publication of those objects. This document provides the protocol for doing so.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"A SLR (Service Level Requirements) based footprint for CDNI" - Haibin Song, Yunfei Zhang</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/song-cdni-slr-based-footprint-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: Footprint advertisement is a very important step for CDN interconnection and generates a lot of discussion. Actually, each CDN can serve the whole world if its surrogates are publicly reachable by IP addresses. But if a CDN does that, it can not satisfy the requirements from the applications. So CDNs deliver contents for applications, and the basic requirements should be from the applications, but there is rare discussion on service level requirements based footprint. This document is used to generate the discussion on this aspect.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"A Self-tuning Distributed Hash Table (DHT) for REsource LOcation And Discovery (RELOAD)" - Jouni Maenpaa, Gonzalo Camarillo, Jani Hautakorpi</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-p2psip-self-tuning-06.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -06: REsource LOcation And Discovery (RELOAD) is a peer-to-peer (P2P) signaling protocol that provides an overlay network service. Peers in a RELOAD overlay network collectively run an overlay algorithm to organize the overlay, and to store and retrieve data. This document describes how the default topology plugin of RELOAD can be extended to support self-tuning, that is, to adapt to changing operating conditions such as churn and network size.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"A TCP transport for the Internet Key Exchange" - Yoav Nir</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/nir-ipsecme-ike-tcp-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: This document describes using TCP for IKE messages. This facilitates the transport of large messages over paths where fragments are either dropped, or packet loss makes them unreliable.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"A Thesaurus for the Terminology used in Multiprotocol Label Switching Transport Profile (MPLS-TP) drafts/RFCs and ITU-T's Transport Network Recommendations." - Huub van Helvoort, Loa Andersson, Nurit Sprecher</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-mpls-tp-rosetta-stone-06.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -06: MPLS-TP is based on a profile of the MPLS and PW procedures as specified in the MPLS-TE and (MS-)PW architectures developed by the IETF. The ITU-T has specified a Transport Network architecture.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"A YANG Data Model for IP Configuration" - Martin Bjorklund</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-netmod-ip-cfg-05.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -05: This document defines a YANG data model for configuration of IP implementations.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"A packet based method for passive performance monitoring" - Alberto Bonda, Alessandro Capello, Mauro Cociglio, Luca Castaldelli</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/tempia-opsawg-p3m-02.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -02: This document describes a method to achieve performance measurements of live traffic, applicable to any packet based traffic stream, including L2, L3, MPLS traffic, unicast and multicast. The method can be easily implemented using tools and features already available on existing routing platforms without any protocol extension and, for this reason, it does not raise any interoperability issue. However, the method could be further improved by means of some extension to existing protocols, but this aspect is left for further study and it is out of the scope of the document.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"AES-CCM ECC Cipher Suites for TLS" - David McGrew, Daniel Bailey, Matthew Campagna, Robert Dugal</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/mcgrew-tls-aes-ccm-ecc-05.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -05: This memo describes the use of the Advanced Encryption Standard (AES) in the Counter and CBC-MAC Mode (CCM) of operation within Transport Layer Security (TLS) to provide confidentiality and data origin authentication. The AES-CCM algorithm is amenable to compact implementations, making it suitable for constrained environments. The ciphersuites defined in this document use Elliptic Curve Cryptography (ECC), and are advantageous in networks with limited bandwidth.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"ALTO Cost Schedule" - Sabine Randriamasy, Nico Schwan</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/randriamasy-alto-cost-schedule-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: The goal of Application-Layer Traffic Optimization (ALTO) is to bridge the gap between network and applications by provisioning network related information. This allows applications to make informed decisions, for example when selecting a target host from a set of candidates. The ALTO problem statement [RFC5693] considers typical applications as file sharing, real-time communication and live streaming peer-to-peer networks. Recently other use cases focused on Content Distribution Networks and Data Centers have emerged [draft-jenkins-alto-cdn-use-cases-01].</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"ALTO Incremental Updates" - Nico Schwan, Bill Roome</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/schwan-alto-incr-updates-02.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -02: The goal of Application-Layer Traffic Optimization (ALTO) is to bridge the gap between network and applications by provisioning network related information. This allows applications to make informed decisions, for example when selecting a target host from a set of candidates.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"ALTO Server Discovery" - Sebastian Kiesel, Martin Stiemerling, Nico Schwan, Michael Scharf, Song Yongchao</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-alto-server-discovery-04.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -04: The goal of Application-Layer Traffic Optimization (ALTO) is to provide guidance to applications, which have to select one or several hosts from a set of candidates that are able to provide a desired resource.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Access Network Identifier (ANI) Option for Proxy Mobile IPv6" - Sri Gundavelli, Jouni Korhonen, Mark Grayson, Kent Leung, Rajesh Pazhyannur</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-netext-access-network-option-11.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -11: The local mobility anchor in a Proxy Mobile IPv6 domain is able to provide access network and access operator specific handling or policing of the mobile node traffic using information about the access network to which the mobile node is attached. This specification defines a mechanism and a related mobility option for carrying the access network identifier and the access operator identification information from the mobile access gateway to the local mobility anchor over Proxy Mobile IPv6.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Additional Data related to an Emergency Call" - Brian Rosen, Hannes Tschofenig, Roger Marshall</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-ecrit-additional-data-04.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -04: When an emergency call is sent to a Public Safety Answering Point (PSAP), the device that sends it, as well as any service provider in the path of the call, or access network may have information about the call which the PSAP may be able to use. This document describes an XML data structure that contains this kind of information in a standardized form. A Uniform Resource Identifier (URI) that points to the structure can be included in the SIP signaling with the call, or the data may be included in the body of a SIP message.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Additional Managed Objects for Network Address Translators (NAT)" - Simon Perreault, Tina Tsou, Senthil Sivakumar</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-behave-nat-mib-02.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -02: This memo defines a portion of the Management Information Base (MIB) for devices implementing Network Address Translator (NAT) function. This MIB module may be used for monitoring of a device capable of NAT function.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Additional Media Type Structured Syntax Suffixes" - Tony Hansen</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-appsawg-media-type-suffix-regs-02.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -02: A content media type name sometimes includes partitioned meta- information distinguish by a Structured Syntax, to permit noting an attribute of the media as a suffix to the name. This document defines several Structured Syntax Suffixes for use with media type registrations. In particular, it defines and registers the "+json", "+ber", "+der", "+fastinfoset", "+wbxml" and "+zip" Structured Syntax Suffixes, and updates the "+xml" Message Type Structured Syntax Suffix registration.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Additional XML Security Uniform Resource Identifiers (URIs)" - Donald Eastlake</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/eastlake-additional-xmlsec-uris-02.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -02: This document expands and updates the list of URIs intended for use with XML Digital Signatures, Encryption, Canonnicalization, and Key Management specified in RFC 4051. These URIs identify algorithms and types of information. This document obsoletes RFC 4051.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Additional negotiation in the TCP Timestamp Option field during the TCP handshake" - Richard Scheffenegger, Mirja Kuehlewind</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/scheffenegger-tcpm-timestamp-negotiation-04.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -04: A number of TCP enhancements in so diverse fields as congestion control, loss recovery or side-band signaling could be improved by allowing both ends of a TCP session to interpret the value carried in the Timestamp option. Further enhancements are enabled by changing the receiver side processing of timestamps in the presence of Selective Acknowledgements.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Alert Metadata Protocol (AMP)" - Matt Lepinski, Karen Seo, Richard Barnes</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/barnes-atoca-meta-03.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -03: This document specifies a set of mechanisms that devices on an IP network can use to discover an alert metadata server able to provide information about local emergency alert services. Additionally, this document provides a protocol that devices on an IP network can use to retrieve local information from an alert metadata server about sources of emergency alerts and register contact information for receipt of alerts.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"An Architectural Perspective on the LISP Location-Identity Separation System" - Yorktown Art</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/chiappa-lisp-architecture-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: LISP upgrades the architecture of the IPvN internetworking system by separating location and identity, current intermingled in IPvN addresses. This is a change which has been identified by the IRTF as a critically necessary evolutionary architectural step for the Internet. In LISP, nodes have both a 'locator' (a name which says _where_ in the network's connectivity structure the node is) and an 'identifier' (a name which serves only to provide a persistent handle for the node). A node may have more than one locator, or its locator may change over time (e.g. if the node is mobile), but it keeps the same identifier.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"An IETF URN Sub-Namespace for OAuth" - Brian Campbell, Hannes Tschofenig</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-oauth-urn-sub-ns-06.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -06: This document establishes an IETF URN Sub-namespace for use with OAuth related specifications.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"An Inquiry into the Nature and the Causes of Web Insecurity" - Hannes Tschofenig, Sean Turner, Mike Hanson</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/tschofenig-secure-the-web-03.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -03: The year 2011 has been quite exciting from a Web security point of view: a number of high-profile security incidents have gotten a lot of press attention but also new initiatives, such as the National Strategy for Trusted Identities in Cyberspace (NSTIC), had been launched to improve the Web identity eco-system. The NSTIC strategy paper, for example, observes problems with Internet security due to the widespread usage of low-entropy passwords and the lack of widely deployed authentication and attribute assurance services.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"An Introduction to the LISP Location-Identity Separation System" - Yorktown Art</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/chiappa-lisp-introduction-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: LISP is an upgrade to the architecture of the IPvN internetworking system, one which separates location and identity (currently intermingled in IPvN addresses). This is a change which has been identified by the IRTF as a critically necessary evolutionary architectural step for the Internet. In LISP, nodes have both a 'locator' (a name which says _where_ in the network's connectivity structure the node is) and an 'identifier' (a name which serves only to provide a persistent handle for the node). A node may have more than one locator, or its locator may change over time (e.g. if the node is mobile), but it keeps the same identifier.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"An XCON Client Conference Control Package for the Media Control Channel Framework" - Chris Boulton, Mary Barnes</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/boulton-xcon-conference-control-package-07.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -07: The Centralized Conferencing framework defines a model whereby client initiated interactions are required for creation, deletion, manipulation and querying the state of a of conference. This document defines a Media Control Channel Package for XCON client initiated Conference Control. The Package is based on the Media Control Channel Framework, which is also used for media server control, thus optimizing the implementation for some entities participating in an XCON system.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Analysis and recommendation for the ULA usage" - Bing Liu, Sheng Jiang, Cameron Byrne</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/liu-v6ops-ula-usage-analysis-03.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -03: This document describes use cases where ULA address may be beneficially used.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Analysis of Port Control Protocol in Mobile Network" - Gang Chen, Zhen Cao, Mohamed Boucadair, Vizdal Ales, Laurent Thiebaut</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/chen-pcp-mobile-deployment-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: This memo provides a motivation description for the Port Control Protocol (PCP) deployment in a 3GPP mobile network environment. The document focuses on a mobile network specific issues (e.g. cell phone battery power consumption, keep-alive traffic reduction), PCP applicability to these issues is further studied and analysed.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Analysis of Security Automation and Continuous Monitoring (SACM) Use Cases" - David Waltermire</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/waltermire-sacm-use-cases-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: This document identifies foundational use cases, derived functional capabilities and requirements, architectural components, and the supporting standards needed to define an interoperable, automation infrastructure required to support timely, accurate and actionable situational awareness over an organization's IT systems. Automation tools implementing a continuous monitoring approach will utilize this infrastructure together with existing and emerging event, incident and network management standards to provide visibility into the state of assets, user activities and network behavior. Stakeholders will be able to use these tools to aggregate and analyze relevant security and operational data to understand the organizations security posture, quantify business risk, and make informed decisions that support organizational objectives while protecting critical information. Organizations will be able to use these tools to augment and automate information sharing activities to collaborate with partners to identify and mitigate threats. Other automation tools will be able to integrate with these capabilities to enforce policies based on human decisions to harden systems, prevent misuse and reduce the overall attack surface.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Applicability of Access Node Control Mechanism to PON based Broadband Networks" - Nabil Bitar, Sanjay Wadhwa, Li Hongyu, Thomas Haag</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-ancp-pon-03.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -03: The purpose of this document is to provide applicability of the Access Node Control mechanism to PON-based broadband access. The need for an Access Node Control mechanism between a Network Access Server (NAS) and an Access Node Complex (a combination of Optical Line Termination (OLT) and Optical Network Termination (ONT) elements) is described in a multi-service reference architecture in order to perform QoS-related, service-related and Subscriber-related operations. The Access Node Control mechanism is also extended for interaction between components of the Access Node Complex (OLT and ONT). The Access Node Control mechanism will ensure that the transmission of information between the NAS and Access Node Complex (ANX) and between the OLT and ONT within an ANX does not need to go through distinct element managers but rather uses a direct device-to-device communication and stays on net. This allows for performing access link related operations within those network elements to meet performance objectives.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Architectural Considerations in Smart Object Networking" - Hannes Tschofenig, Jari Arkko, Dave Thaler, Danny McPherson</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/tschofenig-smart-object-architecture-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: Following the theme "Everything that can be connected will be connected", engineers and researchers designing smart object networks need to decide how to achieve this in practice. How can different forms of embedded and constrained devices be interconnected? How can they employ and interact with the currently deployed Internet? This memo discusses smart objects and some of the architectural choices involved in designing smart object networks and protocols that they use.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Asserting DNS Administrative Boundaries Within DNS Zones" - Andrew Sullivan</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/sullivan-domain-origin-assert-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: Some clients on the Internet make inferences about the administrative relationships among servers on the Internet based on the domain names of those servers. Perhaps unfortunately, it is not currently possible to detect the real administrative boundaries in the DNS, and therefore such inferences can go wrong in several ways. Mitigation strategies deployed so far will not scale. The solution to this is to provide a way to make an explicit assertion about the relationships between services provided at different domain names.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Automatic Key and Adjacency Management for Routing Protocols" - William Atwood, Revathi Somantha</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/atwood-karp-akam-rp-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: When tightening the security of the core routing infrastructure, two steps are necessary. The first is to secure the routing protocols' packets on the wire. The second is to ensure that the keying material for the routing protocol exchanges is distributed only to the appropriate routers. This document specifies requirements on that distribution and proposes the use of a set of protocols to achieve those requirements.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Automating the Initial Window in TCP" - Joseph Touch</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/touch-tcpm-automatic-iw-03.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -03: The Initial Window (IW) provides the starting point for TCP's feedback-based congestion control algorithm. Its value has increased over time to increase performance and to reflect increased capability of Internet devices. This document describes a mechanism to adjust the IW over long timescales, to make future changes more safely deployed and to potentially avoid reexamination of this value in the future.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"BGP Flow-Spec Extended Community for Traffic Redirect to IP Next Hop" - Matthieu Texier, David Smith, Pradosh Mohapatra, Wim Henderickx, Adam Simpson</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/simpson-idr-flowspec-redirect-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: Flow-spec is an extension to BGP that allows for the dissemination of traffic flow specification rules. This has many possible applications but the primary one for many network operators is the distribution of traffic filtering actions for DDoS mitigation. The flow-spec standard [RFC 5575] defines a redirect-to-VRF action for policy-based forwarding but this mechanism can be difficult to use, particularly in networks without L3 VPNs.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"BGP Remote-Next-Hop" - Gunter Van de Velde, Keyur Patel, Robert Raszuk, Randy Bush</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/vandevelde-idr-remote-next-hop-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: The BGP Remote-Next-Hop is a new optional transitive attribute intended to facilitate automatic tunneling within an AS on a per address family basis. The attribute carries one or more tunnel end- points for a NLRI. Additionally tunnel encapsulation information is communicated to successfully setup these tunnels.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"BGP Tunnel Address Prefix Attribute and Tunnel Address Prefix Extended Community" - KuiKe Building, Kai Li</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/xu-idr-tunnel-address-prefix-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: This document describes a new BGP attribute referred to as Tunnel Address Prefix Attribute and a new BGP address specific extended community referred to as Tunnel Address Prefix Extended Community, both of which are intended for facilitating the load-balancing of IP/GRE tunneled traffic (e.g., L3VPN-over-GRE traffic) in the core of IP-enabled Packet Switch Networks (PSN).</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"BGPSEC Protocol Specification" - Matt Lepinski</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-sidr-bgpsec-protocol-04.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -04: This document describes BGPSEC, an extension to the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) that provides security for the AS-PATH attribute in BGP update messages. BGPSEC is implemented via a new optional non- transitive BGP path attribute that carries a digital signature produced by each autonomous system on the AS-PATH.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Benchmarking Methodology for Content-Aware Network Devices" - Mike Hamilton, Sarah Banks</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-bmwg-ca-bench-meth-02.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -02: This document defines a set of test scenarios and metrics that can be used to benchmark content-aware network devices. The scenarios in the following document are intended to more accurately predict the performance of these devices when subjected to dynamic traffic patterns. This document will operate within the constraints of the Benchmarking Working Group charter, namely black box characterization in a laboratory environment.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"CDNI Request Routing with ALTO" - Jan Seedorf</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/seedorf-cdni-request-routing-alto-02.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -02: Network Service Providers (NSPs) are currently considering to deploy Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) within their networks. As a consequence of this development, there is a need for interconnecting these local CDNs. The necessary interfaces for inter-connecting CDNs are currently being defined in the Content Delivery Networks Interconnection (CDNI) WG. This document focusses on the Request Routing Interface of CDNI, and more specifically on how the solutions currently being defined in the Application Layer Traffic Optimization (ALTO) WG can improve CDNI request routing. The overall intention behind this document is to foster discussions (in the CDNI as well as in the ALTO WG) regarding if, how, and under what conditions ALTO can be useful to optimize CDNI request routing. As basis for this discussion, this document provides concrete examples of how ALTO can be integrated within CDNI request routing and in particular in the process of selecting a downstream CDN. The examples in this document are based on the use cases and examples currently being discussed in the CDNI WG.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"CDNI Request Routing: Footprint and Capabilities Semantics" - Jan Seedorf, Jon Peterson, Stefano Previdi</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/spp-cdni-rr-foot-cap-semantics-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: This document tries to capture the semantics of the "Footprint and Capabilities Advertisement" part of the CDNI Request Routing interface, i.e. the desired meaning and what "Footprint and Capabilities Advertisement" is expected to offer within CDNI. The discussion in this document has the goal to facilitate the choosing of one or more suitable protocols for "Footprint and Capabilities Advertisement" within CDNI Request Routing.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Call Flow for CLUE" - Robert Hansen, Arun Krishna, Allyn Romanow</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/romanow-clue-call-flow-02.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -02: This draft shows the CLUE call flow demonstrating the use of CLUE in SIP. It also provides information about the message and syntax for CLUE transport establishment and other extensions in SDP. In CLUE participants act as both providers and consumers. The draft includes a detailed example of a typical use case which includes both static and switched captures.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Carrier's Wifi at Home Network" - Rong Zhang</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/zhang-intarea-wifi-home-network-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: Today operator could share the wifi network at subscriber's home for their public subscribers. It need to upgrade the home router which has integrated wifi already. Some technical requirements have been clarified in this document.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Chatrooms within a Centralized Conferencing (XCON) System" - Mary Barnes, Chris Boulton, Salvatore Loreto</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/boulton-xcon-session-chat-08.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -08: The document "A Framework for Centralized Conferencing" defines a centralized conference as both signaling and protocol agnostic. The primary examples within this framework focus on audio and video as the media types for the session. This document provides an overview of the mechanisms defined in the centralized conferencing framework that can be used to support multi-user chat. In addition, the document describes additional functionality and requirements necessary to provide feature rich functionality.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"CoRE Resource Directory" - Zach Shelby, Srdjan Krco, Carsten Bormann</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/shelby-core-resource-directory-04.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -04: In many M2M applications, direct discovery of resources is not practical due to sleeping nodes, disperse networks, or networks where multicast traffic is inefficient. These problems can be solved by employing an entity called a Resource Directory (RD), which hosts descriptions of resources held on other servers, allowing lookups to be performed for those resources. This document specifies the web interfaces that a Resource Directory supports in order for web servers to discover the RD and to register, maintain, lookup and remove resources descriptions. Furthermore, new link attributes useful in conjunction with an RD are defined.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"ConEx Concepts and Use Cases" - Bob Briscoe, Richard Woundy, Alissa Cooper</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-conex-concepts-uses-05.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -05: This document provides the entry point to the set of documentation about the Congestion Exposure (ConEx) protocol. It explains the motivation for including a ConEx marking at the IP layer: to expose information about congestion to network nodes. Although such information may have a number of uses, this document focuses on how the information communicated by the ConEx marking can serve as the basis for significantly more efficient and effective traffic management than what exists on the Internet today.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Congestion Control Principles for CoAP" - Carsten Bormann, Klaus Hartke</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/bormann-core-congestion-control-01.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -01: The CoAP protocol needs to be implemented in such a way that it does not cause persistent congestion on the network it uses. Congestion control is a complex issue -- the proper rationale for the congestion control mechanisms chosen in CoAP is probably more material than the CoAP protocol specification itself. This informational document attempts to pull out the background material and more extensive considerations behind the CoAP congestion control mechanisms, while leaving the basic MUSTs and MUST NOTs in the main spec.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>"Congestion Exposure (ConEx) Concepts and Abstract Mechanism" - Matt Mathis, Bob Briscoe</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/ietf-conex-abstract-mech-05.txt</link>
  <description>2012-07-16, rev -05: This document describes an abstract mechanism by which senders inform the network about the congestion encountered by packets earlier in the same flow. Today, network elements at any layer may signal congestion to the receiver by dropping packets or by ECN markings, and the receiver passes this information back to the sender in transport-layer feedback. The mechanism described here enables the sender to also relay this congestion information back into the network in-band at the IP layer, such that the total amount of congestion from all elements on the path is revealed to all IP elements along the path, where it could, for example, be used to provide input to traffic management. This mechanism is called congestion exposure or ConEx. The companion document "ConEx Concepts and Use Cases" provides the entry-point to the set of ConEx documentation.</description>
</item>


</channel></rss>
