<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet title="CSS_formatting" type="text/css" href="css/rss.css"?>
<?xml-stylesheet title="XSL_formatting" type="text/xml" href="rss2html.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
><channel>
<!-- Generated with Perl's XML::RSS::SimpleGen v11.11 -->

<link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/</link>
<title>New RFCs</title>
<description>Recently released Request For Comments documents</description>
<language>en</language>
<lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 18:28:27 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<skipHours><hour>0</hour><hour>1</hour><hour>2</hour><hour>3</hour><hour>4</hour><hour>5</hour><hour>6</hour><hour>7</hour><hour>8</hour><hour>9</hour><hour>10</hour><hour>11</hour><hour>12</hour><hour>13</hour><hour>14</hour><hour>15</hour><hour>16</hour><hour>17</hour><hour>19</hour><hour>20</hour><hour>21</hour><hour>22</hour><hour>23</hour></skipHours>
<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
<sy:updatePeriod>daily</sy:updatePeriod>
<sy:updateBase>1970-01-01T18:30+00:00</sy:updateBase>
<ttl>1440</ttl>
<webMaster>webmaster@tools.ietf.org</webMaster>
<docs>http://www.interglacial.com/rss/about.html</docs>

<item>
  <title>6692: Source Ports in Abuse Reporting Format (ARF) Reports</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6692.txt</link>
  <description>(8KB) This document defines an additional header field for use in Abuse Reporting Format (ARF) reports to permit the identification of the source port of the connection involved in an abuse incident.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6686: Resolution of the Sender Policy Framework (SPF) and Sender ID Experiments</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6686.txt</link>
  <description>(26KB) In 2006, the IETF published a suite of protocol documents comprising the Sender Policy Framework (SPF) and Sender ID: two proposed email authentication protocols. Both of these protocols enable one to publish, via the Domain Name System, a policy declaring which mail servers were authorized to send email on behalf of the domain name being queried. There was concern that the two would conflict in some significant operational situations, interfering with message delivery.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6674: Gateway-Initiated Dual-Stack Lite Deployment</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6674.txt</link>
  <description>(32KB) Gateway-Initiated Dual-Stack Lite (GI-DS-Lite) is a variant of Dual- Stack Lite (DS-Lite) applicable to certain tunnel-based access architectures. GI-DS-Lite extends existing access tunnels beyond the access gateway to an IPv4-IPv4 NAT using softwires with an embedded Context Identifier that uniquely identifies the end-system to which the tunneled packets belong. The access gateway determines which portion of the traffic requires NAT using local policies and sends/ receives this portion to/from this softwire. [STANDARDS-TRACK]</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6656: Description of Cisco Systems' Subnet Allocation Option for DHCPv4</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6656.txt</link>
  <description>(54KB) This memo documents a DHCPv4 option that currently exists and was previously privately defined for the operation and usage of the Cisco Systems' Subnet Allocation Option for DHCPv4. The option is passed between the DHCPv4 Client and the DHCPv4 Server to request dynamic allocation of a subnet, give specifications of the subnet(s) allocated, and report usage statistics. This memo documents the current usage of the option in agreement with RFC 3942, which declares that any preexisting usages of option numbers in the range 128-223 should be documented and that the working group will try to officially assign those numbers to those options. This document is not an Internet Standards Track specification; it is published for informational purposes.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6688: Parallel NFS (pNFS) Block Disk Protection</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6688.txt</link>
  <description>(12KB) Parallel NFS (pNFS) extends the Network File System version 4 (NFSv4) to enable direct client access to file data on storage devices and bypass the NFSv4 server. This can increase both performance and parallelism, but it requires additional client functionality, some of which depends upon the type of storage used. The pNFS specification for block storage (RFC 5663) describes how clients can identify the volumes used for pNFS, but this mechanism requires communication with the NFSv4 server. This document updates RFC 5663 to add a mechanism that enables identification of block storage devices used by pNFS file systems without communicating with the server. This enables clients to control access to pNFS block devices when the client initially boots, as opposed to waiting until the client can communicate with the NFSv4 server. [STANDARDS-TRACK]</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6685: Expert Review for Incident Object Description Exchange Format (IODEF) Extensions in IANA XML Registry</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6685.txt</link>
  <description>(4KB) This document specifies restrictions on additions to the subset of the IANA XML Namespace and Schema registries, to require Expert Review for extensions to Incident Object Description Exchange Format (IODEF). [STANDARDS-TRACK]</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6684: Guidelines and Template for Defining Extensions to the Incident Object Description Exchange Format (IODEF)</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6684.txt</link>
  <description>(23KB) This document provides guidelines for extensions to the Incident Object Description Exchange Format (IODEF) described in RFC 5070 for exchange of incident management data, and it contains a template for Internet-Drafts describing those extensions, in order to ease the work and improve the quality of extension descriptions. This document is not an Internet Standards Track specification; it is published for informational purposes.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6677: Channel-Binding Support for Extensible Authentication Protocol (EAP) Methods</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6677.txt</link>
  <description>(78KB) This document defines how to implement channel bindings for Extensible Authentication Protocol (EAP) methods to address the "lying Network Access Service (NAS)" problem as well as the "lying provider" problem. [STANDARDS-TRACK]</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6667: LDP 'Typed Wildcard' Forwarding Equivalence Class (FEC) for PWid and Generalized PWid FEC Elements</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6667.txt</link>
  <description>(17KB) The "Typed Wildcard Forwarding Equivalence Class (FEC) Element" defines an extension to the Label Distribution Protocol (LDP) that can be used when requesting, withdrawing, or releasing all label bindings for a given FEC Element type is desired. However, a Typed Wildcard FEC Element must be individually defined for each FEC Element type. This specification defines the Typed Wildcard FEC Elements for the Pseudowire Identifier (PWid) (0x80) and Generalized PWid (0x81) FEC Element types. [STANDARDS-TRACK]</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6664: S/MIME Capabilities for Public Key Definitions</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6664.txt</link>
  <description>(37KB) This document defines a set of Secure/Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions (S/MIME) Capability types for ASN.1 encoding for the current set of public keys defined by the PKIX working group. This facilitates the ability for a requester to specify information on the public keys and signature algorithms to be used in responses. "Online Certificate Status Protocol Algorithm Agility" (RFC 6277) details an example of where this is used. This document is not an Internet Standards Track specification; it is published for informational purposes.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6663: Requirements for Signaling of Pre-Congestion Information in a Diffserv Domain</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6663.txt</link>
  <description>(15KB) Pre-Congestion Notification (PCN) is a means for protecting quality of service for inelastic traffic admitted to a Diffserv domain. The overall PCN architecture is described in RFC 5559. This memo describes the requirements for the signaling applied within the PCN-domain: (1) PCN-feedback-information is carried from the PCN-egress-node to the Decision Point; (2) the Decision Point may ask the PCN-ingress-node to measure, and report back, the rate of sent PCN-traffic between that PCN-ingress-node and PCN-egress-node. The Decision Point may be either collocated with the PCN-ingress-node or a centralized node (in the first case, (2) is not required). The signaling requirements pertain in particular to two edge behaviors, Controlled Load (CL) and Single Marking (SM). This document is not an Internet Standards Track specification; it is published for informational purposes.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6662: Pre-Congestion Notification (PCN) Boundary-Node Behavior for the Single Marking (SM) Mode of Operation</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6662.txt</link>
  <description>(65KB) Pre-Congestion Notification (PCN) is a means for protecting the quality of service for inelastic traffic admitted to a Diffserv domain. The overall PCN architecture is described in RFC 5559. This memo is one of a series describing possible boundary-node behaviors for a PCN-domain. The behavior described here is that for a form of measurement-based load control using two PCN marking states: not- marked and excess-traffic-marked. This behavior is known informally as the Single Marking (SM) PCN-boundary-node behavior. This document defines an Experimental Protocol for the Internet community.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6661: Pre-Congestion Notification (PCN) Boundary-Node Behavior for the Controlled Load (CL) Mode of Operation</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6661.txt</link>
  <description>(71KB) Pre-Congestion Notification (PCN) is a means for protecting the quality of service for inelastic traffic admitted to a Diffserv domain. The overall PCN architecture is described in RFC 5559. This memo is one of a series describing possible boundary-node behaviors for a PCN-domain. The behavior described here is that for a form of measurement-based load control using three PCN marking states: not- marked, threshold-marked, and excess-traffic-marked. This behavior is known informally as the Controlled Load (CL) PCN-boundary-node behavior. This document defines an Experimental Protocol for the Internet community.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6660: Encoding Three Pre-Congestion Notification (PCN) States in the IP Header Using a Single Diffserv Codepoint (DSCP)</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6660.txt</link>
  <description>(51KB) The objective of Pre-Congestion Notification (PCN) is to protect the quality of service (QoS) of inelastic flows within a Diffserv domain. The overall rate of PCN-traffic is metered on every link in the PCN- domain, and PCN-packets are appropriately marked when certain configured rates are exceeded. Egress nodes pass information about these PCN-marks to Decision Points that then decide whether to admit or block new flow requests or to terminate some already admitted flows during serious pre-congestion.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6658: Packet Pseudowire Encapsulation over an MPLS PSN</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6658.txt</link>
  <description>(31KB) This document describes a pseudowire mechanism that is used to transport a packet service over an MPLS PSN in the case where the client Label Switching Router (LSR) and the server Provider Edge equipments are co-resident in the same equipment. This pseudowire mechanism may be used to carry all of the required layer 2 and layer 3 protocols between the pair of client LSRs. [STANDARDS-TRACK]</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6627: Overview of Pre-Congestion Notification Encoding</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6627.txt</link>
  <description>(46KB) The objective of Pre-Congestion Notification (PCN) is to protect the quality of service (QoS) of inelastic flows within a Diffserv domain. On every link in the PCN-domain, the overall rate of PCN-traffic is metered, and PCN-packets are appropriately marked when certain configured rates are exceeded. Egress nodes provide decision points with information about the PCN-marks of PCN-packets that allows them to take decisions about whether to admit or block a new flow request, and to terminate some already admitted flows during serious pre-congestion.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6670: The Reasons for Selecting a Single Solution for MPLS Transport Profile (MPLS-TP) Operations, Administration, and Maintenance (OAM)</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6670.txt</link>
  <description>(75KB) The MPLS Transport Profile (MPLS-TP) is a profile of the MPLS technology for use in transport network deployments. The work on MPLS-TP has extended the MPLS technology with additional architectural elements and functions that can be used in any MPLS deployment. MPLS-TP is a set of functions and features selected from the extended MPLS toolset and applied in a consistent way to meet the needs and requirements of operators of packet transport networks.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6669: An Overview of the Operations, Administration, and Maintenance (OAM) Toolset for MPLS-Based Transport Networks</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6669.txt</link>
  <description>(45KB) This document provides an overview of the Operations, Administration, and Maintenance (OAM) toolset for MPLS-based transport networks. The toolset consists of a comprehensive set of fault management and performance monitoring capabilities (operating in the data plane) that are appropriate for transport networks as required in RFC 5860 and support the network and services at different nested levels. This overview includes a brief recap of the MPLS Transport Profile (MPLS-TP) OAM requirements and functions and the generic mechanisms created in the MPLS data plane that allow the OAM packets to run in-band and share their fate with data packets. The protocol definitions for each of the MPLS-TP OAM tools are defined in separate documents (RFCs or Working Group documents), which are referenced by this document. This document is not an Internet Standards Track specification; it is published for informational purposes.</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6655: AES-CCM Cipher Suites for Transport Layer Security (TLS)</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6655.txt</link>
  <description>(17KB) This memo describes the use of the Advanced Encryption Standard (AES) in the Counter with Cipher Block Chaining - Message Authentication Code (CBC-MAC) Mode (CCM) of operation within Transport Layer Security (TLS) and Datagram TLS (DTLS) to provide confidentiality and data origin authentication. The AES-CCM algorithm is amenable to compact implementations, making it suitable for constrained environments. [STANDARDS-TRACK]</description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>6644: Rebind Capability in DHCPv6 Reconfigure Messages</title>
  <link>http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6644.txt</link>
  <description>(19KB) This document updates RFC 3315 (DHCPv6) to allow the Rebind message type to appear in the Reconfigure Message option of a Reconfigure message. It extends the Reconfigure message to allow a DHCPv6 server to cause a DHCPv6 client to send a Rebind message. The document also clarifies how a DHCPv6 client responds to a received Reconfigure message. [STANDARDS-TRACK]</description>
</item>


</channel></rss>
